John Cohen collection, circa 1939-2019
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Manuscripts, ca. 1956-2009
  - Subseries 3. Writings and published works, 1956-2002
    - Peru: An Introductory Investigation of Paracas Textiles, ca. 1957, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/269)
      Written by Cohen for the Department of Design.
    - Peru: Paul Hostetter, 1998, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/157)
      Correspondence, sketches.
    - Peru: Natural History, 1957, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/158)
      Magazine includes Cohen's article, "Q'eros: A Study in Survival," Natural History (1957), 482-489, 492-493.
    - Peru: Peru book texts, 1971-1973, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/159)
      Correspondence, notes, drafts, and galleys for potential book about Peruvian weaving.
    - Peru: Peru book texts, 1971-1973, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/270)
    - Peru: Materials for MFA thesis, ca. 1957, 1 notebook (Box 24)
      1 notebook related to Cohen's MFA thesis.
    - Peru: Mountain Music of Peru, 1974, 1 folder (Box 25)
      1 bound book relating to the album, Mountain Music of Peru.
    - Peru: unpublished Peru book materials, 1967, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/162)
      Notes and text set in type for Peru book.
    - Peru: unpublished Peru book materials, 1967, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/272)
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: The Social Organization of a Native Andean Community, 1972, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/163)
      1 book by Steven Webster, University of Washington, Anthropology Ph.D., with Cohen's notes inserted.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero: el Utimo Ayllu Inka, 1983, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/164)
      1 book by Oscar Nunez del Prado. Includes correspondence with Cohen and the Centro de Estudios Andinos Cuzco.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Puna Qheswa Yunga: El Hombre y su Medro en Q'ero, 1989, 1 folder (Box-folder 13/165)
      1 book by Jorge Flores.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero textile book design, 2001-2002, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/166)
      Correspondence and galleys relating to Hidden Threads of Peru.
    - Peru: various academic papers, ca. 1997-2001, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/167)
      Correspondence and academic papers relating to Peruvian culture and textiles.
    - Peru: various academic papers, ca. 1997-2001, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/273)
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: drafts, 2000, 2 folders (Box-folder 14/168-169)
      Drafts, correspondence, captions, and Textile Museum annual report relating to, Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero Textiles book.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero textiles: American Museum of Natural History, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/170)
      1 color slide and 4 color photographic prints relating to Q'ero textiles.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Telluride Festival, 2000, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/171)
      Color copies of photographs relating to Q'ero textiles. These were used for publicity.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Textile Museum, 2000, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/172)
      Correspondence, notes, programs, and color copies of photographs relating to Q'ero textiles and the Textile Museum in Washington, DC.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru: Edward Ranney, 2000, 1 folder (Box-folder 14/173)
      Correspondence and photocopy of photographic prints.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru project, 2000, 4 folders (Box-folder 14/174-177)
      Sketches, maps, correspondence, notes, proofs, and drafts relating to Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero Textiles book.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru project, 2000, 2 folders (Box-folder 19/274-275)
      Sketches, maps, correspondence, proofs, and drafts relating to Hidden Threads of Peru book.
    - Hidden Threads of Peru project, 2000, 2 folders (Box-folder 22/301-302)
      Sketches, maps, correspondence, proofs, and drafts relating to Hidden Threads of Peru: Q'ero Textiles book.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: Bob Dylan, Harry Smith, County Records, 1967-1969, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/178)
      Interview transcripts, drafts of articles, and correspondence relating to County Records. Bob Dylan, Harry Smith, and the RE-issue Issue - County Records.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: Bob Dylan, Janis Ian, 1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/179)
      Notes and correspondence from Izzy Young, and interview transcript relating to Bob Dylan interview and Sing Out! article. Janis Ian interview transcript.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: Janis Ian, 1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 22/303)
      Notes and interview transcript relating to Janis Ian interview transcription and other interviews.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: George Davis, Janis Ian, Cousin Emmy, 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/180)
      Interview transcripts and correspondence, including from George Davis and Cousin Emmy, 1 35mm slide, and drafts of articles.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: George Davis, Janis Ian, Cousin Emmy, 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/276)
      Interview transcripts and correspondence, including from George Davis and Cousin Emmy, notes, and drafts of articles.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: George Davis, Janis Ian, Cousin Emmy, 1967-1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 21/304)
      New Lost City Ramblers, Modern Times album cover.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: University of Chicago Folk Festival, Modern Times, Earl Scruggs, 1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/181)
      Article draft, liner notes draft, and festival program for the University of Chicago Folk Festival. Drafts are for New Lost City Ramblers Modern Times album and Earl Scruggs and the 5-String Banjo.
    - Articles for Sing Out! and Folkways: University of Chicago Folk Festival, Modern Times, Earl Scruggs, 1968, 1 folder (Box-folder 19/277)
    - Folk Art vs. Pop Art: drafts, notes and correspondence, 1966-1989, 3 folders (Box-folder 15/182-184)
      Drafts, correspondence, notes, interview transcripts relating to Sing Out!, "Folk Art vs. Pop Art" article (published in Sing Out! ), and other articles. Inludes correspondence with Moe Asch, Bob Dylan, Pete Seeger, Bruce Jackson, and Robert Frank. Includes a preliminary layout of Cohen's article, "A Visitor's Recollections"; writings about the making of The High Lonesome Sound and The End of an Old Song ,; and a John Hartford interview transcript.
    - Folk Art vs. Pop Art: drafts, notes and correspondence, 1966-1989, 3 folders (Box-folder 19/278-280)
      Drafts, correspondence, notes, interview transcripts relating to Sing Out!, "Folk Art vs. Pop Art" article (published in Sing Out! ), and other articles. Inludes correspondence with Moe Asch, Bob Dylan, Pete Seeger, Bruce Jackson, and Robert Frank. Includes a preliminary layout of Cohen's article, "A Visitor's Recollections"; writings about the making of The High Lonesome Sound and The End of an Old Song; and a John Hartford interview transcript.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: projects and articles, 1961-1963, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/185)
      Correspondence regarding speaking engagements and articles responding to 1960 Mademoiselle article, "Folk Furor."
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: writings, 1949-1950, 1976, 1982, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/186)
      Correspondence, notes, and drafts. Includes "Selections from Neuberger Collection (1982), National Geographic Society photography guidelines, "Creative writing, Great Neck High School," Ike (Isaac Davis) (My First Blues)," "(No Kerouac, no Dharma Bums on the horizon, yet)," letter responding to a New York Times review of Musical Holdouts, notes for Bolivian textile exhibit proposal, notes for Dark Holler.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: John Cohen interview, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/187)
      1 transcription of an interview with John Cohen. Interviewer, Jim Brown.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: writings, 1971-1999, 3 folders (Box-folder 15/188-191)
      Notes, articles, drafts of articles, drafts of liner notes, interview transcriptions, and correspondence. Includes correspondence with Allen Tullos, Ry Cooder, Mike Seeger, and Tracy Schwarz. Liner notes for Dillard Chandler, David Grisman, Roscoe Holcomb albums and other writings concerning The End of an Old Song, The High Lonesome Sound, High Atmosphere, and other of Cohen's projects.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: writings, 1971-1999, 3 folders (Box-folder 19/281-283)
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: American Skyline, 1956, 1 folder (Box-folder 15/192)
      1 book with illustrations by John Cohen. Tunnard, Christopher and Henry Hope Reed. American Skyline: The Growth and Form of our Cities and Towns. New American Library, New York (1956).
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: exhibits and articles, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/193)
      Exhibit labels, catalog, clippings, and proofs. Includes program for exhibit, "Rebels: Painters and Poets of the 1950s," Bluegrass Unlimited article by Cohen, Intro to Peru photos by Herbert Matter, proofs for article, "The Beat Goes On," the American Institute of Graphic Arts (AIGA) show of Cohen's photographs.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: exhibits and articles, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/284)
      Includes Herbert Matter introduction to exhibit.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: exhibits and articles, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 21/305)
      Clippings and proofs for "The Beat Goes On" article about Beat culture.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: articles and programs, 1957-1958, 1960, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/194)
      Magazine clippings, 1 program. "Folk Furor" article in Mademoiselle, "On the Road Again" article in Vogue, "I Got a Witness" article in the Jazz Review, and Ballet Russe de Monte Carlo program.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: liner notes and exhibit programs, 1970-1971, 1977-1978, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/195)
      Magazine clippings, liner notes, and exhibit programs. Includes "The Beat Goes On" interview, High Atmosphere LP liner notes, The Spirit of the New Landscape exhibit program, "Photographs of Peru," Helen Gee and the Limelight program, Carlton Gallery, Mountain Artisans Appalachia program, RISD Mountain Music of Kentucky liner notes.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: liner notes and exhibit programs, 1970-1971, 1977-1978, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/285)
      Magazine articles, interview (1995), exhibit programs, "The Beat Goes On" interview, High Atmosphere LP liner notes, Helen Gee and the Limelight program.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: articles by Cohen, 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/196)
      Exhibit poster, image gallery poster. John Cohen articles in Modern Photography and in Jazz Review magazines.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: articles by Cohen, 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 21/306)
      Image gallery poster.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: various articles, 1954, 1958-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/197)
      Magazines and articles, and sample layouts. Articles from the New York Times Magazine, House Beautiful, Modern Photography, Pulse and Pressure: A Report of Current Views on Hypertension and Related Cardiovascular Disorders, and Jubilee.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: various articles, 1954, 1958-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/286)
      Magazines and articles. Articles from the New York Times Magazine and House Beautiful, as well as Peru sample layouts.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: Twen, ca. 1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/287)
      2 magazines (October and November).
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: exhibits and articles, early years, 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/199)
      Magazine articles, exhibit programs, correspondence, 35mm slides, and notes relating to Reverend Gary Davis. Includes articles from Modern Photography, as well as clippings from Esquire, Seventeen, and Vanity Fair, and New York Public Library Photography sampler booklets.
    - Various writings, published work, and exhibits: exhibits and articles, early years, 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/288)
      Magazine articles from Esquire and Seventeen, and Image Gallery poster.
    - Ephemera: Caravan (folder 1 of 3), 1958, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/200)
      Includes three issues of Caravan Folkmusic Magazine (or, Caravan: the Magazine of Folk Music), one of which Cohen is on the cover (with an article by Izzy Young). Also includes correspondence from Billy Faier (editor) regarding the May 1958 article.
    - Ephemera: Caravan (folder 2 of 3), 1958-1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/201)
      Includes four issues of Caravan Folkmusic Magazine (or, Caravan: the Magazine of Folk Music).
    - Ephemera: Caravan (folder 3 of 3), 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/202)
    - Ephemera: Chooog, Spring 1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/203)
      Spring issue with an inscription from Lee Shaw.
    - Ephemera: Disc Collector, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/204)
      2 issues of Disc Collector magazine, one addressed to Israel Young.
    - Ephemera: Folk Music Guide USA, 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/205)
      4 issues of Folk Music Guide USA, published monthly by the Folklore Center.
    - Ephemera: Folk Style, ca. 1959-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/206)
      Issue no. 10 with New Lost City Ramblers on cover.
    - Ephemera: Folkin' Around, 1965, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/207)
      1 issue containing folk news and schedules.
    - Ephemera: Folkways, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/208)
      1 issue (issue 2).
    - Ephemera: Gardyloo, 1959, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/209)
      Two issues, one with Mike Seeger on the cover, one with John Cohen on the cover.
    - Ephemera: Good News!, September, 1961, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/210)
      1 issue (vol. 1, no. 5)
    - Ephemera: Little Sandy Review, ca. 1960, 4 folders (Box-folder 17/211-214)
      No. 1-30 (with a couple of missing issues). Folk music reviews fanzine, published by Paul Nelson and Jon Pankake in Minneapolis, Minnesota.
    - Ephemera: Hootenanny, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/215)
      1 promotional guide.
    - Ephemera: folk festivals, 1961-1962, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/216)
      University of California Folk Music Festival staff list, University of Chicago Folk Festival program and schedule.
    - Ephemera: magazine clippings, 1959, 1979, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/217)
      Includes article about Lloyd Loar and Esquire photocopied articles.
    - Ephemera: magazine clippings, 1959, 1979, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/289)
      Includes Musician magazine cover and articles from Esquire magazine.
    - Ephemera: papers and programs, 1964, 1981, 1985, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/218)
      Academic paper (by Alan Jabbour), Union Grove Fiddlers' Convention, and "How to Play the Cajun Accordion in No Time at All" (Michael B. McClellan).
    - Ephemera: promotional posters, ca. 1962-2005, 3 folders (Box-folder 23/307-309)
      Promotional posters for the New Lost City Ramblers and other performances, as well as for exhibits of John's photographs, such as There is No Eye.
    - Ephemera: promotional posters, ca. 1959-1966, 2 folders (Box-folder 20/310-311)
      Fliers and posters for New Lost City Ramblers, Friends of Old Time Music concerts, and other concerts, as well as drawing drafts for one of the flier designs. Many of the fliers were designed and/or printed by Cohen. GR001-GR040.
    - Ephemera: fliers and programs, ca. 1959-1964, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/312)
      GR041-GR060. Fliers, posters, and programs for New Lost City Ramblers, Friends of Old Time Music concerts, and other concerts. Includes program for Alan Lomax and Louis Gordon's "Folksong '59" concert at Carnegie Hall
    - Ephemera: fliers and catalogs, ca. 1946-1965, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/313)
      Fliers for New Lost City Ramblers and other performers' concerts, as well as catalogs for Folkways Records and for Disc Company of America. Includes sheet music for "Talking Folklore Center" by Bob Dylan. GR062-GR068.
    - Ephemera: fliers, promotional posters, clippings, ca. 1939-2002, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/314)
      Fliers for screenings of John Cohen's films, exhibits of his photographs, and magazine clippings. Includes tracing of a bronze piece from John Cohen's parents, ca. 1939, Sunnyside Folk Dance Group, Queens, NY. GR079-GR081, GR083-085, GR090, GR106-GR110, GR125, GR134.
    - Artwork, ca. 1955-1960, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/315)
      Drawings, cut outs, and designs of the Hoot events Cohen hosted, made by Cohen during his time at Yale University Department of Design.
    - Old enclosures for fliers and promotional posters, ca. 1959-1965, 1 folder (Box-folder 20/316)
      Original polyurethane sleeves that housed Cohen's fliers and promotional posters.
    - Fieldwork: Penny Cohen, Peru diary, ca. 1964, 1 bound journal (Box 26)
      Penny Cohen's diary during her and John Cohen's fieldwork in Peru.
    - Fieldwork: logbook of Peru recordings, 1964, 1979, 1980, 1982, 1 folder (Box-folder 17/220)
      1 bound book relating to field recordings, as well as correspondence.
  - Subseries 4. Oversize Posters, ca. 1959-2006
    Oversize materials, such as posters, artwork, fliers, and ephemera. Stored at Fort Meade by "OS" folder and GR identifier number (from original order) Scope and content descriptions are from original objects themselves or from transcribing writing on original objects.
    - GR069, undated, AFC 2011059: OS01-GR069; color, 20 1/3 x 30 in.
      Student Folk Concert, Free Trade Hall, Manchester.
    - GR070, undated, AFC 2011059: OS01-GR070; color, 20 1/3 x 30 in.
      Royal Hall-Harrogate. Second Folk Song Concert starring The New Lost City Ramblers, The Calton Three, Shirley Collins, and Owen T. Staley.
    - GR071, 1959, AFC 2011059: OS01-GR071; color, 28 x 22 in.
      Folk Festival USA. Mr. and Mrs. John Sams, Hazard, Kentucky.
    - GR072, 1965, AFC 2011059: OS01-GR072; color, 18 3/4 x 28 1/2 in.
      Direct from U.S.A.: Seeger and The New Lost City Ramblers plus Australia's leading folk singers as presented at the Newport Folk Festival. May 27-29.
    - GR073, undated, AFC 2011059: OS01-GR073; color, 22 1/2 x 13 7/8 in.
      Family dog on the great highway magic at the edge of the Western world.
    - GR074, undated, AFC 2011059: OS02-GR074; color, 14 x 20 1/2 in.
      Northern California Folk-Rock Festival, Santa Clara City Fairgrounds, May 23-25.
    - GR075, November 10, 2013, AFC 2011059: OS02-GR075; black and white, 11 x 17 in.
      Sixth Annual Harry Smith Festival, Millheim Pennsylvania, November 10, 2013 at the Elk Creek Cafe and Aleworks.
    - GR076, 1965, AFC 2011059: OS02-GR076; color, 9 7/8 x 29 1/2 in.
      Royal Hall Harrogate; F.J. Morgan Promotions presents Wrestling; Harrogate Folk Song Society presents the second Folk Song Concert starring the New Lost City Ramblers, The Calton Three and Shirley Collins.
    - GR077, undated, AFC 2011059: OS02-GR077; color, 13 1/3 x 30 in.
      Leeds Student Arts Festival. Folk Concert: New Lost City Ramblers, The Watersons, Colin Ross and Ray Fisher, Bob and Carole Pegg, and Phil Grenfell at Leeds Town Hall.
    - GR078, undated, AFC 2011059: OS02-GR078; color, 16 7/8 x 21 7/8 in.
      Humbead's revised Map of the World with list of population
    - GR099, undated, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR099; color, 22 3/4 x 10 5/8 in.
      [Untitled digital color print drawing depicting a pair of hands playing a banjo. John Cohen and others are in the background on a hill]
    - GR100, February, 1961, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR100; color, 12 x 24 in.
      1st Annual University of Chicago Folk Festival, 3-5, 1961, Leon Mandel Hall.
    - GR101, February, 1962, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR101; color, 11 7/8 x 15 7/8 in.
      2nd Annual University of Chicago Folk Festival, February 2-4, 1962, Leon Mandel Hall.
    - GR102, undated, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR102; color, 14 x 10 in.
      New Lost City Ramblers, Monday, July 26, 8:15 p.m. Edwards Auditorium, Wakefield, Rhode Island
    - GR103, undated, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR103; black and white, 10 x 20 7/8 in.
      New Lost City Ramblers, Reed College; Saturday, April 29, Sport Palace.
    - GR104, undated, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR104; black and white, 11 x 14 in.
      New Lost City Ramblers, Moose Hall: 2nd Floor, Thursday, November 21, 8 p.m.
    - GR105, undated, AFC 2011059: OS03-GR105; black and white, 10 1/2 x 17 in.
      Reed College Cultural Affairs Com. presents, The New Lost City Ramblers Folk Concert, Botsford Auditorium, May 10.
    - GR111, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR111; color, 16 1/3 x 21 1/2 in.
      The Great Hudson River Revival, June 17, Crofton Point Park on the banks of the Hudson
    - GR112, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR112; black and white, 18 x 24 3/8 in.
      The Friends of Old Time Music & Newport Folk Foundation present Music of the Mountaineer: Roscoe Holcomb, Dillard Chandler and Galax String Band: Kyle Creed & Fred Cockerhan, March 26, New School (66 West 12th Street).
    - GR113, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR113; black and white, 24 3/8 x 16 3/4 in.
      John Cohen Films, sponsored by Industrial Design, Liberal Arts, Graphic Design, Rhode Island School of Design auditorium, Friday, May 3.
    - GR114, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR114; color, 16 7/8 x 21 3/4 in.
      Southern Folk Festival, November 9 and 10.
    - GR115, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR115; color, 12 3/4 x 17 1/4 in.
      "Do not miss The Berkely Old time Music Convention," September 14-17, 2006, New Lost City Rambler!
    - GR116, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR116; color, 16 3/4 x 23 1/2 in.
      Latin America, Mexico, Peru, Paraguay: M Alvarez Bravo, John Cohen and Luke Holland: SIDE Photographic Gallery, 9 Side, Newcastle-upon-Tyne.
    - GR117, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR117; color, 23 3/4 x 17 5/8 in.
      International Film: 80 Spring Series
    - GR118, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR118; color, 22 1/4 x 19 1/4 in.
      Proposed record cover by Leonard Stokes [Untitled digital color print drawing depicting a pair of hands playing a banjo. John Cohen and others are in the background a hill]
    - GR119, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR119; color, 14 x 20 in.
      Harry Smith, "A Recreation," orchestrated by M. Henry Jones, Fourth World presents a multi-projection light and sound explosion/legendary Avant-Garde film and animation to be screened as Smith originally intended.
    - GR120, undated, AFC 2011059: OS04-GR120; color, 14 x 22 in.
      Sunset Park on Rt. 1 between West Grove & Oxford, Pennsylvania, May 9, in person Stanley Brothers.
    - GR121, May-September, 1998, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR121; color, 15 x 22 3/8 in.
      Exclusive Exhibition, May 16 through September 3, 1998. Photography by John Cohen and Bob Dylan on Peekskill Hollow Road, Avalon Archives, Tr. 301 Kent Cliffs, New York.
    - GR122, May-September, 1998, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR122; black and white, 15 x 22 3/8 in.
    - GR123, March 7, 2004, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR123; color, 11 15/16 x 17 in.
      John Cohen in concert, March 7, 2004, 7:30 p.m. Hampshire College, Music Recital Hall, Music and Dance Building.
    - GR124, November-December, 2006, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR124; color, 12 x 18 in.
      Avalon Archives Museum of Rock & Roll presents The Filmore, The Avalon, and "The Good ol' Grateful Dead" at The Howland Cultural Center, 477 Main Street, Beacon, New York, November 4-December 17, 2006.
    - GR126, undated, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR126; color, 14 x 22 1/4 in.
      The Hoots Yale Folk Singers in a concert, March 19, at the St. Elmo Society, 111 Grove Street.
    - GR127, February 18, 1967, AFC 2011059: OS05-GR127; color, 15 3/8 x 20 1/4 in.